Hi, welcome to the first official video
in my new apartment.
So, here's the thing. We've a lot of
organizing to do.
It's like 5:30 already. I got stuff to
make dinner.
Like I just like have not been in the
mood to cook. And what I think it is is
because of this weird food illness thing
going around cuz all I want to eat is
fruits and vegetables and lettuce and
salad.
And like I'm scared, but I have been
eating arugula. So, I'm going to make an
arugula salad for dinner.
Actually, let me show you around.
And this is like real and raw of like
the things that we've got done. I didn't
clean anything up and I have a lot to
clean up. But, we're getting a lot done,
okay? The kitchen, these are clean, just
things that cannot be dishwashed.
Um
my ice machine all got stuck together,
so I had to throw out all the ice and
now I have no ice, but
that's okay. This little nook besides
the banana and the water. I'm loving my
little nook right here. I think I want
to get a real toaster.
Um you guys have had this bottle of
tequila since college graduation 4 years
ago. And
I don't know, I can't throw it out
because it's like expensive, but also no
one's going to drink it. Like I'm not
drinking that. So, I'm leaving it out
and whoever comes over next
is going to get it as a gift. Let's see.
So, George hung up these curtains, which
are really, really nice. This is so much
more clear than it used to be. These are
my old bar stools. They actually look
amazing. I got a bunch of deliveries, so
I have stuff to put away.
The couch, we're getting rid of, sadly.
It just doesn't fit in the space.
Obviously, we've already placed an order
for another one. And then the bedroom, I
would say we've made the most progress
in. Hi new mirror spot. I've also had
this mirror forever, and I think I'm
keeping her. I wish it was like a little
bit warmer. Like it's kind of like this
gray color, but I really don't care
right now. Um eventually, we will be
replacing
the nightstands. I don't know my
thoughts on the bed. Like I just feel
like it doesn't go with the vibe I'm
going for. But I love my striped bed
frame, so what I think we're going to do
is store it at George's mom's house, and
then when George and I buy a house in
the future, we keep our bed frame. Like
perfect idea, right? And this beautiful,
beautiful dresser, I'm obsessed with it.
We had a TaskRabbit.com do the TV, so
now I can be all cozy in bed. And then
also we did the same
um what are these called? Curtains in
here, but weirdly
this side, so I bought like four packs
of two.
I don't know if you can tell, but they
have oil stains all over them. Maybe it
was this one where you could really see
it.
I feel like of course now you can't see
it now. Okay, you can kind of see it.
Not really. Like
right here. It must have been like some
sort of like corner.
And then if you could tell up there,
like I don't know. Really upset about
that, also like grossed out, so we
replaced those. We got to take those
ones down because like ew. The bathroom
is a mess. Like this is what I really
need to tackle today because I've been
getting annoyed that I can't find any of
my products, so then I rummaged through
this box, and then it just looks like
that. And we did have to put a shower
curtain up, which is also kind of crazy
because they told us that they were
putting glass in, and then they said
that they weren't doing glass because it
was a design and I'm like
how can you just shower Like look, if we
didn't have this, we were showering for
a couple days without this.
Like
fully a tub. Like if we didn't put the
curtain up, like water gets everywhere.
They said they're eventually putting uh
glass thing a glass door up.
So that's fine. We couldn't wait
anymore, so we ended up getting this
shower curtain. Like wouldn't have been
my first choice, but we just needed
something for the temporary time being.
Also taken over George's space. Does he
have a whole mirror to himself?
Absolutely not. He gets half a shelf,
and that's kind of me.
Like honestly, George doesn't really
have that many products. The only other
thing is like these
these drawers are so nice that there's
three of them, but they're a little bit
shallow. So, I can't stick products
upright, which is totally fine. I have a
bunch of these that we're just going to
have to figure out. I decided we're
going to make dinner first and then
organize.
Honestly, not really feeling like
organizing the bathroom right now
because mentally I have to just like
be in the zone, you know? My goal is to
really just put everything away in that
dresser so that I'm no longer living out
of boxes and bags. Making this like
Greek yogurt
chicken that I keep seeing all over the
place, but I have never tried it.
You touch the raw chicken.
But, we're freezing the other
and being an adult, you know?
I am very curious to see how this comes
out, but apparently it makes it like
moist and yummy.
We will see about that.
George is not here for the night, so I
really want to go to bed early
and have tea and then read my book. I
feel like we've just been up late every
single night doing so much stuff around
the apartment. I'm making the girliest
meal that he would probably never want
to eat.
I put way too much garlic powder and
it's like flying up my nose. [snorts]
I also really need to fill my salt and
pepper shakers,
but I keep putting it off. That's like
the most annoying chore to do. Like, I
never fill up my salt and pepper
shakers.
So, I just realized well, actually it
looks pretty good. Honestly.
But, it says that I should let it I
should have let this sit for like 15 to
30 minutes, but like
it's already almost 6:00. I don't feel
like doing that. So, we're just going to
put it in the air fryer.
Um yeah, so we just went to do the
dishes.
And I sprayed myself. I grabbed this
while the water was on, and I'm so not
used to that because my old apartment
and the nozzle came down.
That's on me. That's on me.
Okay,
clean clothes. Learning ingredients. I
just flipped the chicken. It's looking
really good. And the peach is delicious.
It's finally like
prime peach season, and I feel like I
need to go back and get a bunch of
peaches and make like a peach cobbler.
That used to be my favorite freaking
dessert
when I was younger. Like my mom would
make it homemade.
And I feel like I could slay a peach
cobbler. Does that not look like a
perfect chicken?
Like wow. I literally slayed this
chicken. It's so
juicy.
Wait, let's try the end piece.
Mhm. Wow, wow. Bed of arugula, red
onion, flaky salt, gorgeous peaches.
Goat cheese. This is not
really crumbling the way I would want it
to. I guess I thought it was going to be
more like feta. And pecans.
And topping this with our gorgeous Greek
yogurt chicken.
Wow. I'm more hungry than I thought
because now that I have this in front of
me, I'm like, ooh, I cannot wait
to eat this.
We also have the Halls. [snorts]
Halls or Howls? Howls?
Best sparkling water legit ever. A lot
of people don't like fruit in their
salad.
I'm not one of those people, clearly. I
love fruit in my salad. Cheers. This is
a big bite.
Mhm.
I'll start making my chicken like this
more often because, oh my god,
so good.
My ice machine is so loud.
I was getting sucked into scrolling and
we got to nip that in the bud because I
have a problem. Let's clean up. I also
can't wait to have a sweet treat. I now
have so much more space in this
apartment, so I have a What's the brand?
I think it's a
>> [clears throat]
>> No, no, no. It's a Ninja. I don't know.
I got some ice cream
machine. I don't even know why I'm
telling you that because I don't have
ice cream to make, but I was just
thinking about it and I have it in a
cupboard and I was like, "We
I should like run to the store and make
a recipe so then I could have it
tomorrow night." Giving the rest of our
juicy chicken.
Fridge also needs major organizing.
I'm going to just I'm obsessed with
these. It's a literally just It's walnut
date cake cubes. It's literally just
walnut and dates smashed together.
It's so good.
Mhm.
I love dates.
I also have a garbage disposal in this
apartment, which is a humongous deal.
Okay, so the kitchen is clean. I still
have to put the drawers away, but now
that I have this idea in my head of
making this healthy ice cream with my
new NutriBullet ice cream maker,
I feel I have to run to the store to get
the ingredients so that I can enjoy it
tomorrow and freeze it overnight and
have this amazing treat. And like,
you know, why move to New New City
if it's not for the benefit of having
convenience at all times. So, we're
going to run to a little store. We
actually already have most things. We
just have to get vanilla pudding mix and
Fairlife milk.
Looks like they don't have Fairlife.
Okay, we got the stuff.
They didn't have vanilla pudding mix,
but like
time, we'll figure it out. I also don't
think I have enough Greek yogurt
to suffice for this. We got Chobani.
I've actually never tried the Chobani
Greek yogurt because I'm very loyal to
my Fage Fage. Ingredients acquired. I'm
so excited to try.
Just washed my thing. Like the this is
not necessary for me to do at all right
now, but
I really wanted to. I'm interested in
the Chobani Greek yogurt. Like
see what this is about.
It's looking like a lot less thick
than the Fage Fage.
I really could have gone to another
store and got the vanilla pudding. Let's
see how this turns out. I was like,
okay, we can't give in to the impulses
more than we already have.
Mhm.
It's good,
but I definitely taste a difference and
I don't like it as much
as the Fage.
It's like
more yogurty.
I don't know how to explain it. Like
it is still Greek yogurt, so like not
hating it, but like
really kind of weird.
I've also never had Fairlife milk
before. Okay, I feel like this is a
pretty small portion
they're making of this. This is 120 g,
which is like half a cup.
Which I put half a cup in my oats of
milk, splash of vanilla extract.
I'm going to do vanilla stevia.
Just a pinch of salt and that's it.
My favorite ice cream is like moose
tracks, which let me explain this. I'm
not the biggest peanut butter lover in
the world. Like I don't like straight up
peanut butter. Like peanut butter cups,
obviously I love like skinny dipped. So
and I just got a huge package from
skinny dipped. So I think I'm going to
chop up a bunch of things
and put it in there after it's frozen.
I'm like really intrigued by this. I
feel like I missed out on the whole like
ninja creamy
virality moment. Okay, this smells
really good.
This is it. This just has to go in the
freezer
for 24 hours.
So I'll let you know how this comes out.
Okay, we're finally doing drawers.
These are all my PJs. [snorts] Okay,
well, not that. That's a random skirt. I
don't know if I have that going in
there. Believe I said this was me
cutting back on my PJs.
Like I know I have a really bad
addiction. I don't want to have to
refold all of these, but I feel like I
kind of need to.
I don't think they're going to all fit
in one drawer, so I'm thinking
we do
long sleeve in one drawer and short
sleeve in another.
One drawer done. I did keep probably
half of them in this bag because a lot
of these Some of these I think I'm going
to get rid of cuz I just don't need
them. And then a lot of these are like
seasonal, like fall and winter. I'm
probably going to end up just putting
them under my bed.
But for now they're going there.
We have skirts. I'm going to organize
this by
midi skirts. These are all midi length.
And then minis and then like short
shorts. It's how I fold my skirts, okay?
So then they're all in the drawer facing
up. I kind of fold my pajamas and
t-shirts, anything that goes in drawers,
this is how I fold it, okay?
You want it to be perfect.
Lay flat. I usually don't do all this.
Like this is a little bit extra, but
this is like kind of long and slippery
material. So, make sure that it is even.
We're going to fold this all the way up
to the top, tuck in the sides,
flip it again,
and flip it again.
So then, you're left with this gorgeous
rectangle. And then, you can just place
it in your drawer
where it needs to go, and you can see
everything. Once this fills up, it'll
have more structure. Like right now,
it's a little lopsided. Knee skirts.
Obviously, I can't put stuff away
without trying on. How sick? I don't
even know if you could tell. It's this
like very dark brown
faux leather skirt from Kookai I just
got in the mail today.
As I was putting away my skirt drawer,
oh my god, I can't wait to wear this in
the fall.
Shorts. This is as organized as it's
going to get. Okay, my hair definitely
needs to be washed.
Well, actually, it really doesn't. Like
I did just wash it, but I think probably
just because I'm walking around so much,
I feel like my hair is getting greasier
faster. I also just like love having
fresh hair. But, I'm going to the 7:00
a.m. SoulCycle class. Well, you know
what? Yeah, I'm going to say that I'm
going to the 7:00 a.m. and manifest it
because I'm wait-listed number one,
which means like
I'm in.
Which Can somebody explain to me why
SoulCycle does this like silly little
thing
where they text people like, "Oh, a spot
might have opened up. Press one to claim
the spot." Even if you're not like the
next in the waitlist. Like
if I get that text and
I'm like no like I got that text the
other day. I was like literally number
12, and I was like, "Oh, one." And I got
the spot. And I was like, "Oh, that's
lit." But like if I'm number one in the
waitlist,
and then like I don't get the spot, like
annoying. But anyways, I'm probably
going to get in. So, then also like now
being in New York, it's like fighting to
the death to get into a workout class,
which I didn't know. Like you really got
to book that in advance. Here's our
challenge. Completely showered before my
tea kettle
tea kettle goes off. I can't speak. This
girl needs some self-tan. Saving my
self-tanner with my moisturizer because
you guys like to say that my face tanner
is crusty.
But you know what? I have to say to
that,
I would rather have a crusty tan
than be pale. Sue me. That's my truth
and I'm speaking it.
Actually, someone did give me the hack
of mixing the drops right into the
moisturizer. Like I used to layer the
two and I will say
I owe that person a big fat kiss,
whoever told me to do that because you
were right. It does go on so much more
even. How cute are these Dairy Boy PJs,
freshly washed.
Oh, but also I got a PR package from
Glossier and the theme of it was I heart
New York. And this one is the I heart
New York balm.com. It's like an apple
one and then they also had like a little
apple keychain
and I felt like it was fitting and I
actually used the keychain for my new
house keys cuz I was like, "Wait,
perfect timing."
Favorite tea. Yes, I have tea every
night even if it's summer.
This is the lavender mint from the brand
Rishi and I was just in Whole Foods the
other day and they actually have some
really good flavors that I need to try.
This is this new tea kettle is so nice,
but it's massive
and I always feel like I'm going to burn
myself.
Remind myself I'm out of my
multivitamin, the women's health.
And I didn't get today.
But, I've been trying this Lummy Skin
firming hydrating
um
hyaluronic acid. I don't even know.
Honestly, I don't even care if it does
anything or not because it tastes so
good. It tastes like candy.
Whoop. It literally tastes like a peach
ring. Wait, because I'm impatient, I
want to check on the yogurt mixture. I'm
not going to try to mix it up.
But, like it's already frozen. I'm going
to try it.
Never mind.
Only the top of it is frozen. Let's make
my oats.
Okay, I think since I have this Fairlife
milk,
we're going to try it in my overnight
oats.
We're tucking them into bed.
Bye-bye. 10:23. Honestly,
not that bad. I would like to be asleep
in the next hour. I'm finally going to
pick back up on my book. I'm still
reading The Girl with the Dragon Tattoo.
Honestly, I would have been done with it
because it started to get really good
and I don't even remember the last thing
I read was, but I have not picked up my
Kindle in probably over a month. So,
it's time to get back into it. I just
like get into these habits where I'm
scrolling every single night until I
fall asleep.
And I need to get back into reading
because it's so much better for you and
it feels so much better and I sleep
better. And like the scrolling, I know I
probably said a lot just because like
recently it's been really bad for me and
like
I need to cut that Like we're
done, okay?
So, yeah.
Going to read my book.
Um my microwave I The thing is
everything in this new apartment is so
high-tech.
I don't know how to use it. So, the
microwave wasn't working and my tea got
kind of cold. So, now I'm just drinking
like lukewarm tea. Not really ideal, but
for the life of me I could not figure
out
how to get the microwave to work and
chat wasn't really helping me either.
So,
my building is probably sick of me
emailing them, but I'm going to be like,
"Hi, um
teach me how to use this. Like, is it
broken? Is it me? Like, what's up?"
But anyways,
I feel like I didn't organize as much as
like I really anticipated it, but I
still did a really good night. And yeah,
I'm excited to be back into our flow of
things.
Things are finally starting to like get
done. The TV for the other room and the
media console comes in next week. No
idea when the new couch is going to come
in,
but I'm not going to be impatient, so
this is really like exposure therapy.
And
it's all work in progress. I need to
remind myself. George said to me the
other day that you need to enjoy the
journey,
which I don't do a lot because I always
want the end product. And that was
really good advice.
If that helps someone else, like I
really hope it does because
I need to just like enjoy. Like, we're
young, hot, engaged, and enjoying the
journey of curating our dream apartment.
So, we need to live in that moment. And
honestly,
being there makes me feel better.
So,
yeah.
Happy Friday. I love you guys. Trying to
get back on track. Trying to get back on
track to our weekly upload. So, thank
you for watching and I love you.